In this short video, I'm going to say a few words about a variation on local
在这段短片中，我要说几句关于LOCAL的一个变种
optimization that applies directly to assembly code called Peephole
直接应用于称为窥视孔的汇编代码的优化
Optimization. The basic idea here is that instead of optimizing on intermediate code
优化。这里的基本思想是，不是对中间代码进行优化
we could do our optimizations directly on assembly code And people optimization is
我们可以直接在汇编代码上进行优化，而人员优化是
one such technique. The peephole is, stands for a short sequence of usually
一种这样的技术。窥视孔是，代表一小段通常
continuous instructions. So, the idea is that we have our program. We can see, we
连续不断的指示。所以，我们的想法是我们有我们的程序。我们可以看到，我们
can think of it as a long sequence of instructions and our peephole is some
我可以把它看作是一个很长的指令序列，我们的窥视孔是一些
window onto this program. So, if we have a peephole of size four, we can think of
打开这个程序的窗口。所以，如果我们有一个大小为4的窥视孔，我们可以想到
ourselves as staring through a small hole at the program and all we can see is a
当我们透过一个小洞盯着节目看的时候，我们所能看到的只是一个
short sequence of four instructions and then we can optimize that sequence. So,
四条指令的短序列，然后我们可以优化该序列。所以,
then we can slide the peephole around and optimize different parts of the program
然后我们可以滑动窥视孔并优化程序的不同部分
And the, what the, what the optimizer will do is it will, you know, stare at this
优化器要做的就是，你知道，它会盯着这个
short sequence of instructions and if it knows a better sequence it will replace
短指令序列，如果它知道更好的序列，它将替换
that sequence by the other one and then it will repeat this as I said. You know,
这个序列加上另一个，然后它会重复这个，就像我说的。你知道,
applying other transformations to, to possibly the same or other parts of the
将其他转换应用于，可能与
assembly program. So, people optimizations are generally written as replacement
汇编程序。因此，人员优化通常被编写为替换
rules. So, the we'll have the window of instructions on the left. So, it'll be
这是规矩。所以，我们会把说明窗口放在左边。所以，这将是
some sequence of instructions and we'll know some other sequence of instructions
一些指令序列，我们就会知道一些其他指令序列
that we would prefer on the right. So, if we see this instruction sequence on the
我们更喜欢坐在右边。所以，如果我们在
left, then we'll replace by the one on the right-hand side. So, for example, if I
左边的，那么我们换成右边的那个。所以，举个例子，如果我
have a move from register b to register a and then I move back from register a to
从寄存器b移到寄存器a，然后我从寄存器a移回
register b well, that's the second move is useless, can, can just be deleted as a way
寄存器b好的，那第二步是没用的，可以，可以只删除一种方式
to replace this two instruction sequence by a one instruction, instruction
将这两条指令序列替换为一条指令、指令
sequence. And this will work provided that there's no possible jump target here. So
序列。如果这里没有可能的跳跃目标，这是可行的。所以
if, if there's no possibility that the code would ever jump to this instruction
如果，如果代码不可能跳到这条指令
then that instruction can be removed. Another example, If I add i to the
则可以删除该指令。另一个示例是，如果我将i添加到
register a, and then I subsequently add j to the register a, I can do a constant
寄存器a，然后我随后将j加到寄存器a，我可以做一个常数。
folding optimization here, and combine those two add two additions into one
这里是折叠优化，然后把这两个加起来加成一个
addition where I add the sum of i = j to the register A. So, many but not quite all
加法，我把i=j的和加到寄存器A上。所以，很多，但不是全部。
of the basic block optimizations that we've discussed in the last video, can be
在我们在上一个视频中讨论的基本挡路优化中，
cast also as peephole optimizations. So, for example if we are adding zero to a
投射也可以作为窥视孔的优化。例如，如果我们要将零加到一个
register and we're storing it in another register, well, that can be replaced by a
寄存器，我们将其存储在另一个寄存器中，该寄存器可以替换为
register move. If we're moving a value from the same register to itself so this
登记搬家。如果我们将一个值从同一个寄存器移到它自身，那么这个
is like a self-assignment, well, that instruction can just be deleted, replaced
就像自赋值一样，那么，指令可以直接删除、替换
by the empty sequence of instructions. And together for those two instructions would
通过空的指令序列。对于这两条指令，加在一起
be those two optimizations, excuse me, would be able to eliminate adding zero to
如果是这两个优化，打扰一下，将能够消除将零加到
a register. So, first this would get translated into a move from a to a. And
收银机。所以，首先，这将被翻译成从a到a的移动。
then the move from a to a would get deleted. And as this little example
那么从a到a的移动将被删除。就像这个小例子
illustrates just like with local optimizations, people optimizations have
说明了与局部优化一样，人员优化具有
to be applied repeatedly to get the maximum effect. I hope this simple
反复使用以获得最大效果。我希望这很简单
discussion has illustrated for you that many optimizations can be applied directly
讨论为您说明了许多优化可以直接应用
to assembly code and that there's really nothing magic about optimizing
汇编代码，优化并没有什么神奇之处
intermediate code. So, if you have a program written in any language, source
中间代码。因此，如果您有一个用任何语言编写的程序，请参阅源代码
language, intermediate language, assembly language. It makes sense to talk about
语言，中间语言，汇编语言。谈论这件事是有意义的
doing transformations of programs written in that language to improve the behavior
对用该语言编写的程序进行转换以改进行为
of the program. And it's also a good time here to mention that program optimization
项目的一部分。这也是一个很好的时机来提到程序优化
is really a terrible term. The compilers do not produce optimal code and it's
真的是个可怕的词。编译器不会产生最佳代码，而且它的
purely an accident if a compiler were to somehow generate the best possible code
如果编译器以某种方式生成尽可能好的代码，这纯粹是一种意外
for a given program. Really, what compilers do is they have a bunch of
对于给定的程序。真的，编译器所做的是他们有一堆
transformations that they know will improve the behavior of the program. And
他们知道将改善程序行为的转换。和
they'll just improve it as much as they ca N. So, really what program optimization is
他们只会尽其所能地改进它。那么，程序优化到底是什么呢？
all about is program improvement. We're trying to make the program better but
所有的一切都是关于程序的改进。我们正在努力使程序更好，但是
there's no guarantee that we will reach the best possible code for a given program.
不能保证我们会为给定的程序编写尽可能好的代码。